今晚要和提安娜一起表演
performing with Tiana tonight.
你不如打造一首诋毁他的歌
Why don't you spit some napalm
埋葬他
on a diss track and bury him
和他在乎的一切
and everything he cares about.
艺人监理部没有人有能力能管理这个交易
There is no head of A&R to oversee the deal.
我们雇佣了泽维尔罗森 谁
We hired Xavier Rosen. Who?
考虑到盖哲思女士受到的威胁
Given the dangers to Ms. Gathers,
法庭允许保释
the court agrees to grant bail.
令我最骄傲的是
What I was most proud of
你收买了那个医生钱了
was that you paid off that doctor.
知道自己跟自己父亲如出一辙感觉怎么样
How does it feel to know you're just like your daddy?
我不得不处理掉几个人 嗯
I had to put in work on a couple of cats. Mmhmm.
那三个想致我们于死地的人
The three horsemen who wanted us dead.
不 还有第四个
Well, there was a fourth horseman.
但肖恩 他不是个告密的人
But Shine, he ain't no snitch.
酷琦 我们没有那么不一样
Cookie, we're not that different.
我真的相信我们可以做到
I truly believe we can make this work.
唱得很好听 哦 那
That was hot. Oh, so...
一开始你恨我 然后又爱我的不得了
first you hate me, then you love me.
你根本不知道
You have no idea...
自己的价值
... what you're worth.
对我的攻击就是对
An attack on me is an attack
你们每个人的攻击
on each and every one of you.
卢修斯和安德鲁想要开战
Lucious and Andre Lyon want a war.
那我们就开战
So we war.
是吗 你觉得这感觉对吗
Yeah, that feel right to you?
我觉得你可以把低音弄得重一些
I think you could make that bass a little harder.
是的
Yeah.
我知道我们有一段时间没有一起合作了
Look, I know we haven't worked together in a while,
但我很感激你来了
but I appreciate you coming through.
感觉这将是很了不起的作品
Feel like this is about to be something big.
想不出来比你更合适的人选
Couldn't think of anyone better.
哦 拜托 小贾
Oh, come on, Mal.
你知道我们一起做的音乐有多好
You know we make good music together.
是的
Yeah.
是的 的确很好
Yeah, we do.
但我们只需要做音乐 德里克
But that's all we need to do, Derek.
我们一起去杀几个里昂家族的人
Let's go kill some Lyons.
你听到了 我们行动吧
You heard him. Let's roll.
现在 你知道我喜欢在上班前和你喝杯咖啡
Now, you know I love getting coffee with you before work,
但总要有一天
but one of these days,
你得让我把咖啡送到你床前
you got to let me bring it to you in bed.
哈 虽然 我有可能喜欢这样
Huh. Well, I might like that,
在遥远未来中的某一天
one of these days in the far future.
哦 未来 好吧
Oh, the future, okay.
这么不给力 没 没有糖 没有奶油
Come on. No... no sugar? No cream?
哦 没有 我喜欢浓的黑咖啡
Oh, no. I like mine dark and strong.
啊 那么 你还需要改进一下
Ah, well, you're gonna have to do a little better than that
如果你想我们有进一步发展
if you want to get in these drawers.
在这里右转
Make a right right here.
小心警察
Watch out for the cops.
确保托尼让他的人散开
And make sure Tony has his guys fan out.
好的 先生
Yes, sir.
在那个热狗摊那边
And we got three marks over there
有三个人盯梢
at that hot dog stand.
你看到那个拿着报纸的人了吗
Now, you see that dude with the newspaper?
没人还看印刷的报纸
Nobody reads print anymore.
我从来都没想过
I never thought I'd be making
坐装甲看医生
doctor visits in an armored personnel carrier.
但是 我了解肖恩 他肯定会报复
Well, I know Shine; he's gonna clap back.
所以你要想出去
So if you want to step your ass out
试试自己是不是防弹的 请便
and see if you're bulletproof, go ahead.
我再试着联系下内莎
I'ma try Nessa one more time.
又给内莎发信息
Still texting Nessa again?
你什么时候才会弄到手
When you gonna hit that?
我会的
I will.
我想让她见我女儿
I want her to meet my daughter.
可爱的小孩子 总是能俘获女孩子
Cute little babies, that always gets the girls.
我总以为是你的饶舌技巧让你撩到妹
I thought it was your rap skills that got the honeys.
那个 也有用
That, too.
我要邀请她参加我的现场音乐会
I'ma invite her to my livestream concert.
一但她看到我的表演 就到手了
Once she sees me doing my thing, it's game over.
那样就够了
That's gonna be enough?
够了
Period.
找到他了 是的
Get him. Yeah.
他的那个贱人也要挨枪子
And that bitch of his gonna catch a few of these, too.
那你为什么费这么大劲
So why are you going through so much trouble
宣布你要竞选市长
to announce you're running for mayor?
要我的话就通知了几个记者 好
I say just call a couple reporters... Right.
宣布一下 然后继续
... do the damn thing, and keep it moving.
你知道 我只想对任何他们
Well, you know, I just want to be prepared
问的问题有所准备
for any questions they might throw at me.
哦 是的 例如
Oh. Yeah, questions like,
你为什么要和有前科的人约会
uh, Why are you trying to date an excon? Huh?
是的 他们可能会问那个 但是 听着 我只会说
Yes, they may ask that. But, look, I'll just say,
我还没到三垒 所以
I haven't been to third base yet, So...
除非我们往下一步发展 你懂的 今晚就三垒
Unless we're planning on, you know, changing that tonight.
不行 明天要去见我的假释官
No. I got to see my P.O. Tomorrow.
你还在假释期
You still have a parole officer?
是的 这叫监管释放 所以
Yeah, it's called supervised release, so...
小心 议员 不好意思 里昂小姐
Heads up, Councilman. Excuse me, Ms. Lyon.
你需要跟我们走一遭
You need to come with us.
后退 额 我不
Step back. Uh, no, I don't.
我都不认识你
I don't even know who the hell you are.
好吧 让开
All right, stand down.
这是怎么回事 先生们
What's going on here, gentlemen?
无意冒犯 议员
All due respect, Councilman.
夫人 是你丈夫派我们来的
Your husband sent us, ma'am.
为了你的安全 他不是我丈夫
For your own safety. He is not my hu...
跟我们走 夫人 他不是我丈夫
Come with us, ma'am. He's not my husband.
听着 我不知道他这次做了什么
Look, I don't know what he did this time.
后退 后退
Stay back. Stay back.
手拿开
Get your hands off of me!
抱歉
I'm sorry!
在录音室熬到很晚嘛 兄弟
Long night at the studio, huh, brother?
吃些鸡蛋吧 兄弟
Get some of these eggs, man.
我做了很多
I made plenty.
早上好 帅哥
Good morning, sunshine.
唷
Yo...
肖恩 你在干什么
Shine, what the hell are you doing?!
你怎么在这里
What the hell are you doing here?!
你和他搞到一起了
You smashing this dude?
不管他和他爸对我的所做所为吗
After what him and his father did to me?
你的淤青是这样来的嘛 安德鲁
That's how you got the bruise, Andre?
我们发生了点分歧
We had a disagreement.
哦 我们有分歧
Oh, we had a disagreement.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
肖恩 看着 我
Shine, look at me.
走开 内莎 看着我
Get out the way, Nessa. Look at me!
你是我哥哥 我爱你
You're my brother, and I love you.
我没有其他亲人了 你知道的
I ain't got nobody else! You know that.
我不会让你为了这个缠上官司 看着我
And I will not have you catching a case over this. Look at me.
我们走
Let's go.
我们离开 肖恩
Let's go, Shine.
肖恩
Shine...
不 肖恩
No! Shine!
我不会在她面前动手
I don't get my hands dirty in front of her.
但是我还会再来的
But I'll be back.
事实上 我会把你留到最后
In fact, I think I'll save you for last.
嘿 兄弟
Hey, brother.
替我的朋友说声抱歉 兄弟
Sorry about my friends, man.
有时候 他们
Sometimes they, uh...
有点失控
they get out of hand.
我房子外面的保安是什么情况
What's with all the security outside my spot?
我星期五的直播表演没问题 对吗
We're good for my livestream show on Friday, right?
说不好 哈基姆
Not exactly, Hakeem.
卢修斯 你怎么不告诉他
Lucious, why don't you tell him.
像我以前说的 一但肖恩
As I was saying, once Shine
再进入到我的势力范围
reentered into my orbit,
我就知道总有一天
I knew there was gonna come a time
他需要教训一下
in which he needed to be corrected.
很幸运的是 昨天晚上
So fortunately, last night,
我的大儿子和我都认为
my eldest son and I decided
他的所为是极其不尊重人的
that his actions were extremely disrespectful
如果 不加以管教
and, if left unchecked,
会威胁到这个家庭 所以我们
a threat to this family. And so we...
教训了他一顿
... checked his ass.
怎么教训的
Checked him how?
你觉得怎么教训的
How you think?
除了肖恩现在在我的地方试图报复
Except now Shine is at my place trying to clap back.
我很抱歉 贾马尔 不会再有下一次了
I'm sorry about that, Jamal; it won't happen again.
我会搬到老爸的客房的
I'm moving in to Pop's guesthouse.
不 小安
No, Dre.
相信我 你不会想什么都依赖他
Trust me, you don't want to be all up under him like that.
等等 我们现在连朋友都打了
Hold up. We beating up our friends now?
儿子 他不是你朋友
Boy, he is not your friend.
听着 你们所有人 我们跟他混在一起
Look, all of y'all, the only reason why
的唯一原因是为了阻止塔里克
we are even messing with him is to block Tariq
立案告我们 你们明白了吗
from building a case against us, you got that?
现在 我们到底如何要怎么阻止他
Now, how in the hell are we gonna stop him
对我们动真格的
from flipping out on us now?
因为肖恩不是个告密的人
Because Shine is not a snitch.
他情愿死也不会当个告密小人
He'd rather be dead than be a rat.
我发誓 我是唯一一个
I swear, am I the only one...
看 你就爱这种闹剧
See, you love this type of drama.
是 他的确是
Yeah, he does.
这不是让我的家人又聚在一起了吗
It brought my family back together, didn't it?
和肖恩一起做的音乐是我最好的一些音乐
The music I'm doing with Shine is some of my best stuff.
那么 你不得不先搁置一段时间了
Well, you're gonna have to postpone that for now.
我已经告诉我的歌迷要发行新歌
I already told my fans it's happening.
我不管你跟歌迷讲了什么
I don't care what you told your fans!
现场直播不能重来啊 老妈
Ain't no doovers in live streaming, Mom.
你要是脑袋中枪了 也没法重来
There also ain't no doovers if you get shot in the head.
听着 听着 不要紧张 没有人要改变任何事
Look, look, relax. Ain't nobody changing anything.
所有事情还是按计划来
Everything stays according to what we're doing.
每个人只需提高警惕 规规矩矩
Everybody just needs to be alert and stay in their lane.
然后等你和那个恶心的议员
And then soon as you're done playing house with...
玩完过家家
the mayor of Dingleberry,
你欠我一支提安娜的单曲
you owe me a Tiana single.
贾马尔 你可以继续
And, Jamal, you can go back to doing
做在你没做音乐时候做的那些事
whatever you do when you're not making music.
你想帮助这个家 那就帮
You want to help the family? You help the family.
你想拯救这个世界 那就拯救世界
You want to go and free the world? Free the world.
但是 小哈 你的帝国娱乐极度流的表演
But, Keem, your Empire XStream show
按计划进行
goes on as planned.
我们必须提高订阅者数量
We got to keep pushing them stats up.
肖恩现在就在我想要他在的地方
I got Shine exactly where I want him.
现在是时候解决他了
Now it's time to tuck his little bitch ass in.
他来了 哈基姆
There he is! Hakeem!
怎么了 弟弟
What's up, little brother?
你对这个曲子有感觉吗
You feeling this track?
你已经知道了
You already know.
上车
Get in.
哟 你可以暂停嘛
Yo, can you pause that?
哟 你想要
Yo, you want it?
我要做什么
What I got to do for it?
让你的极度流的表演更有卖点 你和我一起
Make your Empire XStream event a double bill. You and me.
拜托 大哥 这是我自己的秀
Come on, bro, I'm doing my own jam right now.
我知道 哈基姆 但是
No, I get it, Hakeem. But listen,
我们可以给粉丝们他们在全美金曲奖上错过的
we could give the people what they missed out on at the ASAs.
而且实话告诉你 我也很需要这个
And keeping it real, I need it, too.
我要让我的粉丝知道 我还没退出乐坛
It's important that I show the fans that I'm still in the game.
大哥 你都没法上台表演
Bro, you can't even perform.
你自己也清楚 在一大堆
You know that. Not in front of
人面前 还有那些欢呼声下 是不行
a big crowd with all these bells and whistles, no.
但是我觉得我们可以在我家客厅表演
But I was thinking we could do it at my living room.
以一种非常亲民的方式
We could make it mad intimate
给粉丝一个惊喜
and just blast it out to the fans.
可能吧
Maybe.
哈基姆和贾马尔 里昂兄弟
Hakeem and Jamal, the Lyon brothers.
现场直播
Live and alive.
你知道那句名言吗
You know the message that that sends to the world?
如果我们不能为后世所铭记
Why we even doing music
那做音乐还有什么意思呢
if we don't make a real imprint on the next generations?
你知道这是怎么回事吗
You know what this is about?
你和爸爸
You and Dad.
是你想和他结束恶性循环的问题
That End the cycle Beef you got with him.
不是的
Nah, man,
是因为你和贝拉
it's about you and Bella.
是因为我们的父亲 她的爷爷
It's about the fact that our father... her grandfather...
打了你最爱的音乐制作人
beat up your favorite producer.
你真的想让她在这样的环境下长大吗
That's really the type of world you want her to grow up in?
我们去拉维特克斯
We're going to Laviticus.
好的 里昂先生
Yes, sir, Mr. Lyon.
好了 听着
All right, listen.
大家还好吗 我是你们的贾马尔 里昂
What's up, y'all? It's your boy, Jamal Lyon.
我是他的宝贝弟弟 哈基姆
And I'm the smooth baby brother, Hakeem.
我们要宣布一件特别的事
And we have a very special announcement.
说吧 小哈 不 你来说 小贾
Tell 'em, Keem. Yeah. Nah, you tell 'em, Mal.
好吧 这周五 一定要锁定我们
All right, look, this Friday make sure y'all are tuned in,
八点整 我们有一个特别的节目
8 o'clock... we have a very special event.
美女们 记得刷 #基姆队 一整天
And look, #TeamKeem, all day, ladies.
你们知道那是什么的
Yeah, yeah. Y'all know what that is.
你们两个小丑
Hey, what kind of funboy stuff
在这干什么幼稚的事呢
y'all two clowns doing up there, man?
喂 这个家伙在
Hey, yo, what this dude doing
我们的地盘上干嘛呢 哎 等等等等
in our spot for, man?! Yo, yo, yo...
你觉得我在干嘛
What it look like I'm doing, man?
我是来找你的 你是说唱歌手 挑战我啊
I'm coming at you. You a MC. Battle me.
你现在就想挑战我吗 小子 小哈
What, you want to go right now, little man? Keem...
不 我们当着你粉丝的面对决
No, let's do it in front of your subscribers.
让他们看看
Let them enjoy the show.
我也会带上我的粉丝
I'ma bring my subscribers, too.
我设计了自己的流媒体应用还有等等
I designed my own little streaming apps and everything.
我可不需要老爹的钱来做这些事
I didn't need daddy money for that.
但是我是个绅士
But since I'm a gentleman,
所以下面就是我会对你做的事 听着
that's what I'ma do for you, okay?
我会让你在几秒钟之内
I'ma have you bloody and trending worldwide
就在全世界面前血流成河
in a matter of seconds.
对镜头笑一笑 你们都喜欢自拍 不是吗
Say Cheese For the camera. Y'all like selfies, right?
是 为粉丝什么都行
Yeah, anything for the fans.
多谢你了
Thank you.
我们要走了
We're gonna leave, man.
我要去找他谈谈 等等 别去 过来
I got to go talk to him. Wait, stop. Come here!
你比他好多了 我们都是
You are better than that. We are better than that.
看着我
Look at me.
用点脑子 行不行
Start using your mind, all right?
有这么多保镖
How the hell did he even get up in here
他怎么还能上来这里
with all of this security around?
卢修斯
Lucious.
我们有了首很棒的新歌
So, we have that great new song,
星光 提安娜很喜欢
Starlight. Tiana loves it,
我觉得是时候录歌了
and I think it's time to record it.
我不觉得这能作为主打单曲
Well, I don't think it's a lead single.
她在拉维特克斯唱的那首歌
Now, the song she did at Laviticus is
热度已经很高了 而且数据显示
already getting crazy heat. And the numbers show...
我们能不能先不提数据
Can we just stop with the numbers really quickly?
我和提安娜谈过了 那首歌不是她想要的
I actually spoke to Tiana, and that song is not what she wants.
贝基 艺人监理部不能总是
Well, Becky, in A&R, we can't always
让步于艺人的想法
give in to what the artist wants.
别用这种语气和我说话
Do not mansplain to me.
尤其是别以这种白人的口气和我说话
And especially do not whitemansplain to me.
那你就别这么无知
Then don't be uninformed.
如果这个消息能让你好受点的话
Now, if it makes you feel better,
我们可以在专辑里
we can throw an experimental track
加上一首实验歌曲 首先 这个不关乎我的感受
deeper in the album. This isn't about how I feel,
其次 我不同意
first of all, and secondly, I disagree...
你说的一切
with everything that you are.
好了 先把枪都放下
Okay. Let's put down the guns.
好吧
All right?
这位屋顶上的小提琴手说的有道理
Fiddler on the Roof here has a point.
他更有远见
He's looking at the bigger picture.
我也同意他说的
And I agree with him.
提安娜唱的那首歌热度的确很高
That song Tiana did is getting crazy heat,
所以我们就要录那首歌 好吗
so that is the song we will record. Okay?
好了 让我们握手言和吧
All right, now, can't we just all get along?
亲亲抱抱
Kiss and make up.
千万别
Don't.
内莎
Nessa.
谢谢你能来
Thanks for coming.
你没事吧
You okay?
没事 我
Yeah, I...
到底发生什么了 小安
What the hell is going on, Dre?
你觉得你和我上床了
You think you can just hook up with me
就能背着我去
and then not tell me that you just got done
蹂躏我的好朋友吗
stomping out my best friend?
我们就是这样的关系吗 我应该告诉你的
That's what we doing? I should've told you.
我无能为力
I couldn't help it.
那我们现在怎么办
So what do we do now?
卢修斯想和肖恩坐下来好好谈谈
Lucious wants to have a sitdown with Shine
让事情回到正轨
and get things back on track.
什么 坐下来谈
What? A sit...
我保证 内莎
I promise you, Nessa,
我们不会再找他麻烦的
we're not gonna screw him over.
最好别 小安
You better not, Dre.
因为他是我唯一的亲人了
Because he's all I got.
过来 不
Come here. N...
过来 过来 过来
Come here. Come here. Come here.
我知道你只有他一个亲人了
I respect that he's all you got.
你可以有更多的
You could have more.
你来看我的时候说的话
What you said when you came to see me...
如果你能有我的音乐天赋
if you had my musical talent...
那是什么意思
what did you mean by that?
帮我把肖恩找过来谈谈
Help me get Shine to the table.
我就告诉你那是什么意思
I'll show you what I meant by that.
好了 小哈 你准备好了
All right, Keem, you ready to put...
见到我很惊讶吗
You look surprised to see me.
惊讶
Surprised.
见到我的儿子我就开心 即使不是我想见的那个
But happy to see my son, even if it's the wrong one.
好吧
Okay.
听着 我有个好消息
Well, look, I have good news.
哈基姆正在努力忘掉他和格拉姆之间的不愉快
Hakeem is squashing that little pettyass beef with Gram.
是的 我
So, yes, I...
我失去了芙蕾达 但是我不会再失去哈基姆
I lost Freda, but... I'm not losing Hakeem.
你干嘛要往自己住的玻璃房砸砖头呢 儿子
Why are you throwing bricks when you live in a glass house, son?
你难道忘了 你为了把芙蕾达
Have you forgotten all those lies you told
弄出来而撒的那些谎了吗
in order to get Freda out of that place?
我做了我该做的事 是啊 然后
I did what I had to do. Yeah, and then
又把她给扔回贫民窟去
you dropped her ass back off in the projects.
莎士比亚说过
You know, Shakespeare said,
你必须对自己诚实
To thy own self be true.
你越快接受自己就是年轻版的我的
The sooner you accept that you are the younger version of me...
升级版本 你就越快能重回
with a twist... the sooner you'll be
舞台 像你以前一样
back on that stage and be your old self again.
就是这个地方
It's this space, man.
上次我坐这把椅子的时候 我和妈妈反目
Last time I sat in this chair, I turned against my mother.
因为她活该
Because she deserved it.
那你呢
And what do you deserve?
你怎么变得如此堕落的
How you get so corrupt?
你不可能天生就是这样的
There's no way that you were born this way.
贾马尔 你生来就有50%的预设基因会让你变成我
Jamal, you are 50% genetically predisposed to become me.
这是无法避免的
It's inevitable.
你知道我喜欢小哈什么吗
You know what I like about Keem?
他知道他和我喜欢的东西一样
He knows that he likes what I like,
而且他清楚他会变得和我一样
and he knows he's going to become me.
他只知道你告诉他的
He knows nothing except what you told him.
也许你该放手让他做自己想成为的人
Maybe you should let him be the man he wants to be
而不是变成你期望的那种人
instead of the man that you want him to be.
天哪 小贾 你太老套了
Oh, my God, you are so corny, Mal.
只要上帝同意 我都准备帮你预约
I'ma book a duet with you and Mary Magdalene,
抹大拉的玛利亚:耶稣从其身体里驱逐出7个恶灵的女人
和抹大拉的玛利亚合唱了
soon as God gives me the okay.
哎呀 我(上帝)不同意
Oops. I said no.
美女 你好啊
Hey, girl. How you doing?
你真漂亮 是不是瘦了
You look good! You lost weight.
胡里欧 我的朋友 哦
Julio, my man. Oh.
夏莲娜 霍落威
Sharlene! Holloway.
嘿 美女 我买了你最爱吃的
Hey, girl, I bought you your favorite.
省省吧 你迟到了 什么
Keep it. You're late. Excuse me?
你预约是早上九点 现在已经九点四十五了
Your appointment was 9:00 a.M. It's a quarter to 10:00.
我知道 但是我每次都是这个时候来的
I know, but I always come here at this time.
你看起来有点生气 我能做点什么吗
You seem a little off. Is there something I can do?
你的监管释放明确规定了
The rules of your supervised release stipulate that
如果你要迟到 必须要提前联系我
you need to contact me if you're going to be late.
我要把这次记下来
I'm gonna have to write you up.
发生什么了 夏莲娜
What's going on, Sharlene?
我不明白你的意思
I don't know what you mean.
上次我来这的时候
Well, the last time I was here,
你还给我看了你孩子的照片
you were showing me pictures of your kids, and...
你这次的态度却截然不同
now you're acting brandnew.
说到那件事
About that.
你上次来这儿都是三个月之前的事了
Your last visit was three months ago.
既然你看不懂时间 我们就要让你
Since you can't tell time, we're going to have to have you
每周来这里报道三次
report here three times a week.
夏莲娜 别这样 拜托
Oh! Sharlene, no, come on, now.
你知道我要经营公司
You know I run a company.
我没法一周来三次
I can't come here three times a week.
你不是在和某些暴徒说唱歌手
This isn't some thug rapper
谈条件 霍落威
you're negotiating with, Holloway.
这里是美国政府
This is the United States government.
你要是需要时间考虑
You need time to consider,
我可以把你送回丹伯里监狱慢慢考虑
I can send you back to Danbury to think it over.
现在 你要去趟厕所
Right now, you need to use the bathroom.
我们赶快解决这个吧
Let's just get this over with.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我知道你们都不想来录我这首歌
I know you're not excited to come in to record Me.
我知道 这是酷琦要求的
I get it... it's what Cookie wants.
如果我告诉你 你来这实际上是
What if I told you that you're actually here
录制星光的呢
to record Starlight
因为这将是你的主打单曲
because it's about to be your lead single?
什么 酷琦不是说
What? I thought Cookie said that...
不是 我 我说服她了
No, I... I talked her out of it.
我告诉她你会进录音室
I told her that you were gonna get in that booth
把这首歌做得很棒
and slay the hell out of that song,
然后她就同意了
and she... agreed with me.
你说真的吗 百分百真的
Are you serious? Dead serious.
天呐 太感谢你了
Oh, my God! Yo, thank you!
你最好了
You're the best.
你知道我就像你背后的内衣扣一样支持你 亲爱的
You know I got your back like bra straps, girl.
哟
Yo!
我总是懂你想要的 没错
I'ma always get you what you want. Yeah! Yes!
过去 我曾以仁爱的名义乞求一块面包
I asked for bread in the name
人们却对我置之不理
Of love and mercy, but humanity did not heed me.
今后我要用邪恶的名义去夺取
So now I shall take it in the name of evil.
她怎么老在睡觉
Why's she always sleeping?
小孩子就是这样的 儿子
'Cause that's what babies do, son.
他们喜欢睡觉
They sleep.
但你没办法这么做
But you can't afford to do that.
你看 作为这个家族的长者
You see, as a patriarch of the family,
你的责任就是去
you're responsible for
教导你的下一代们如何在这个冰冷的世界里存活下去
teaching your young ones how to survive in this cold world.
贾马尔不懂
Jamal don't understand that.
他觉得这个世界都是
He thinks it's all
康巴(歌颂人权的赞歌)和爱 但是他错了
Kumbaya and love, but he's wrong.
是杀戮 或被杀戮
It's kill or be killed.
是吞噬 或被吞噬
Eat or be eaten.
听着 我知道你努力
Look, I know you're trying
想教导我在你手下
to get me up under you
像是安德鲁在你手下那样
like how you got Andre up under you.
我要你把格拉姆给灭了
I want you to crush Gram
因为这能给帝国娱乐赚很多钱
because it means money for Empire,
并且帝国娱乐极度流也需要这些
and Empire XStream needs that kind of
吹嘘和炒作
fanfare and activity.
但是我要你把他毁了
But I want you to destroy him,
因为你是里昂家族的一员
'cause you're a Lyon,
我要让全世界知道
and I want the world to know
没有人能玩弄你
that you're not someone to be trifled with.
我要这个小女孩知道他的父亲是怎样的一个人
I want this little girl to know what kind of man her daddy is.
为什么每个人都要把贝拉牵扯进来
Why is everybody bringing Bella into this?
因为 像你一样
Because, like you...
她出生在里昂家
she was born a Lyon.
所以她生下来就已经被牵扯进去了
So she's born into this.
看到这本书了吗
See this book?
卡里 纪伯伦写的
It's written by Kahlil Gibran.
叫作 泪与笑
It's called A Tear and a Smile.
里面有一个罪犯的故事
Inside it is the story of The Criminal.
讲到一个年轻男人
It tells of a young man...
非常热心的一个人
who was very kind of heart,
他依靠着他的善良 与人道
and he depended on the kindness of humanity
想要混口饭吃
in order for him to eat.
但过不了多久 他就发现他快要饿死了
But after some time, he found himself starving to death.
然后就在你觉得他差不多要死去的时候
And right when you thought he was about to die,
他意识到了他自己真正的天性
he realized his own true nature.
看看 小基 人类的本性
You see, Keem, the nature of humanity isn't
不是爱与和平 而是黑暗和残暴
love and peaceful, it's dark and beastly.
它将温顺与谦和推向罪恶
And it'll turn the meek and the humble into a criminal,
和平之子则成为
and the sons of peace into...
毁灭人的毁灭者
destroyers of men.
他变成了毁灭人的毁灭者
He became a destroyer of men.
因为他不得不这么做
Because he had to.
这是
What is... ?
呃 一个问题 你能别这样表演吗
Um, one, can you not do the stool like that?
这让你看起来像是要发飙
It makes you look pissed.
还有就是 你真心跑到界外去了
And then also, you are literally out of bounds.
这是这场表演的目的
That's what all this tape is for.
你现在看起来就像是 在我的阳台上
You're, like, in my balcony.
整个表演太软弱了
Yo, this whole performance is too soft.
它需要给人肃然起敬的感觉 小贾
It needs to command respect, Mal.
为什么你现在说话和卢修斯一样
Yo, why you sounding like Lucious now?
哈基姆 我们明天就要表演了 好吗
Hakeem, our performance is tomorrow, okay?
他们重新安排了我的整个公寓 我们有一首歌
They're rearranging my entire apartment, and we have a song.
一首酷毙了的歌 这是酷毙了 但是这一段
A dope song. It is dope, but this verse,
我需要用来回击所有和我作对的人
I need to use to clap back to my haters.
不 你不需要
No, you should not.
你知道吗 如果你打算今后的
You know what, you're literally
整个音乐生涯都去做回击唱片
gonna stand your whole career doing clapback records.
没关系 我不在乎
That's fine, and I don't care,
但是请你在别人的音乐里做这些
but do it on someone else's track,
因为 我不允许你放这种鬼话在我这儿
'cause you're not gonna put that B.S. On mine.
我们签协议了吗
We got terms and conditions?
如果你有足够的粉丝
If you had enough followers,
你就可以在你自己的频道做这些 而不是帝国娱乐极度流这里
you'd be doing this on your own channel, not Empire XStream.
你知道吗 老弟 你快惹恼我了
You know what, bro, you about to piss me off.
哥 你是才需要这个节目的人 不是我
Bro, you're the one that needs this, not me.
你是掉粉过气的那个 不是我
You're the one that's losing his fans, not me.
现在 如果需要签约的话
Now, if it's gonna be terms and conditions,
想想看吧 那也得按照我的条件
just think about it... it's mine.
因为 众所周知
'Cause everybody knows
这场音乐会决定着你的生死
this concert is life or death for you.
想想看吧
Just think about it.
举起手
Arms up.
嗨 不用这样吧 兄弟 如果我带了武器
Hey, come on, man. Hey, if I was packing,
我就违背了坐下来谈的条件了
I would have violated the terms of the sitdown.
你们这是对我的侵犯
This is a violation.
如果我想要侵犯你
If I wanted to violate you,
肖恩 你会被顶着抢搜身
Shine, you'd be getting patted down with some bullets.
呵 是嘛
Yeah. Is that right?
我有四个枪手在外头说
Well, I got four shooters outside
你不敢这么干
that say you won't.
不 你只有三个
No, you got three.
还有一个在五星酒店里
One stayed back at a fivestar hotel,
现在应该正在享受我送去的客房服务
where he's getting some room service sent up by me right now.
如果你喜欢的话 我现在可以给你在外面的兄弟
And if you like, I can send your boys outside
也送点点心
a snack, too.
别忘记我也是做这个的 肖恩
Don't forget I do this, Shine.
不 你不是做这个的 卢修斯
No, you don't do this, Lucious.
我做这个
I do this.
你多年没做了
You ain't did this for years.
你有了事业 而我还在混街头
You industry. And I'm still in the streets.
如果我必须要毁掉某人的话
And if I got to blow somebody up,
我不介意同归于尽
I don't care if I die with him.
但是你已经知道了
But you already know this.
听着 也许我们的开头
Look, maybe we got off
不太顺利
on the wrong foot, huh?
喝点什么吗
You want a drink or something, man?
不了 有话直说
No, I'm straight.
我们可能会艰难地谈一晚上
'Cause we can talk tough all night.
但我记得之前
But last time I checked,
我们和内莎之间的进展很好
we had something real good going with Nessa.
没错 我也这么觉得
Yeah, I thought so, too.
在你和你儿子试图离间和攻击之前是的
That's until you and your son tried to divide and conquer.
你自找上门的
You came at us first, man.
这是什么
What is this?
我们在做什么
What are we doing?
算了吧 卢修斯 是我 兄弟
Come on, Lucious, it's me, bro.
我本应该早就埋了你的
I could have buried you a long time ago
用任意一个现在已经变成尸体的人
with any one of them bodies you got.
你忘记卡姆登了吗
You forget Camden?
等等 兄弟
Hold on, man.
你可是在跟我说话
It's me you're talking to.
口口声声叫我 兄弟
Calling me Bro,
却要提起这样的事
and you're gonna bring something like that up?
这些我完全不知道是什么东西的事情
Which I don't know what the hell you're talking about.
不过如果我确实知道
But if I did,
那这就是违反谈判规定了
that would be violating code right here.
好 你知道吗
Okay, you know what?
你们在浪费我的时间
This is a waste of my time.
算了吧 内莎 我们走
Come on, Nessa, let's move.
肖恩 嘿 我听说你来了
Shine. Hey, I thought I heard you in here,
把我女儿都吵醒了
waking up my baby.
阿妮卡 我们事情正谈到一半
Look, Anika, we in the middle of something right now.
噢 好的 你和他说过我们讨论过的事情了吗
Oh, good. Did you tell him about the idea that we discussed?
我的好老公
My husband,
就在不久前 我们刚刚说到
just the other day, he had just said
他有多么感谢能有你在他身边
how much he really appreciates having you around here.
你知道 帮哈基姆做音乐
You know, putting your ear to Hakeem,
带来内莎
bringing in Nessa.
他甚至说真的很惭愧
He even said that it was such a shame
你的才能被埋没了这么久
that your talent had been slept on all this time, and...
想象一下你要是有自己的团队能做什么
imagine what you could do with your own imprint.
是吗 宝贝
Right, babe?
但是 你知道 我是说 如果你需要人
But, you know, I mean, if you ever need somebody
帮你跨过一些障碍 我就在这儿
to bounce anything off of, I'm here.
尽管告诉我
Just let me know.
很开心见到你
Good to see you.
这是你的条件么 卢修斯
Is that what you're offering, Lucious?
我自己的团队
My own imprint?
我刚正想说这件事
That's what I was trying to get to
你就已经变身金刚了 兄弟
when you came charging in like King Kong or something, man.
内莎也是交易的一部分吗
Is Nessa part of that deal?
听着 内莎和帝国娱乐已经签的合同和这个不同 但是
Look, Nessa's under a different contract with Empire, but...
我们可以两相结合
we can crosspollinate, man.
芙蕾达 盖茨呢
What about Freda Gatz?
我听说她退出了
I heard she out.
我听说她很厉害
I hear she's dope.
嘿 如果芙蕾达能为你所用 那她自然是你的 兄弟
Hey, if Freda gets it done for you, she's all yours, bro.
芙蕾达很赞 肖恩
Freda's the one, Shine.
这对你来说是个很好的交易
And this could be a good deal for you.
对我而言
Oh, for me, huh?
对我们大家 肖恩
For us, Shine.
成交
We got a deal.
欢迎加入帝国娱乐 亲爱的
Welcome to the Empire, baby.
嘿 你还好吗 我差不多结束了
Hey, you okay? I barely got through,
哦 最后两个会议
uh, last two meetings.
你和我的假释官见过了吗
You been talking to my probation officer?
什么 没有啊
Say what? No.
为什么要我做这个
Why would I do that?
所以 这完全是一个巧合 在我和你说完
So, it's a total coincidence that after I tell you
我处在监管释放状态之后
I'm on supervised release,
我的假释官就开始对我执行严格的监管了吗
my P.O. Starts acting strict with me.
不 我真的一点都不知道 不是我
No, I don't know nothing about that. It's not me.
嗯 那一定是因为你在竞选市长
Hmm. Then it must be because you're running for mayor
然后你想要我在你控制之下
and you want to keep me in check.
好吧 听着
Oh, uh, okay, look,
我没有控制女人的习惯
I don't make a habit of keeping women in check.
你把我和你的前夫弄混淆了
You must've got me confused with your exhusband.
别提卢修斯
Leave Lucious out of this, man.
哦 怎么可能不
Well, how can I?
他肯定
He's making sure
和这件事脱不了干系
he's very much a part of this.
你这是什么意思 安吉洛
And what the hell is that supposed to mean, Angelo?
酷琦 听着 我想要理解你 我知道你也知道
Cookie, look, I'm feeling you. Okay, I know you know this.
但是你和卢修斯
But you and Lucious,
你们之间很多问题都还没有解决 你需要考虑这些
y'all got some unresolved issues you need to take care of.
我唯一的问题就是被告知我有问题
My only issue is being told what issues I have.
听着 安吉洛
See, Angelo,
你根本不了解我 我不了解 我怎么可能了解
you don't know me like that. I don't. How can I?
你根本没让我了解 每次我尝试
You don't let me. Every time I try
走近你 你总是把我挡在墙外
to get close to you, you put a wall up.
哦 看 就是这样
Aw, man... See? Look, there you go.
我不能 好吧
I can't! What? Okay.
那今晚就先这样吧
Uh, let's just cut this night short,
好吧 我们现在说话都比较轻率
all right, 'cause we're both getting reckless in the mouth...
那是 我们中的某个人会说一些
Yeah. ... and one of us is gonna say something
我们会后悔的话
that we're gonna regret.
我已经说了
Already did that.
晚安，酷琦
Good night, Cookie.
好吧，晚安
Yeah, well, good night.
谢谢 祝你好运
Thank you. Good luck.
我知道
I know.
你还是没有听从直接的命令
Yet you still disobeyed a direct order,
还有你跟提安娜撒谎了
and you lied to Tiana.
这不是蛇爬滑梯游戏
This ain't Chutes and Ladders.
而是音乐生意
It's the music business.
我想你们应该懂我说的生意是什么意思
I thought you people understood what the word Business Meant.
你知道 酷琦会很生气的
You know, Cookie is going to be pissed.
我知道 这就是为什么我要你先听听这首歌
I know. That's why I wanted you to listen to the song first.
你能帮我劝劝酷琦这歌真的会非常火
You can help me convince Cookie that this song is a hit.
我不知道它有多火 不不不，你知道的
I don't know that it is a hit. Yes, you do!
这歌很棒 你听听
The song is dope. Listen to it.
更重要的是，这是艺人自己想要的
More importantly, it's what the artist wants.
我们明天要做的就是让酷琦听听这歌
All we have to do is let Cookie hear it tomorrow.
她会喜欢的，所有账都会一笔勾销的
She'll love it, and all will be forgiven.
听听她唱的
Listen to her.
我要把我清洁工的号码给你
I'ma give you the number to my cleaning lady,
因为这地方太恶心了 哈基姆
because this place is disgusting, Hakeem.
我应该早知道有一天你会跑回去找妈妈的
I should've known you would have ran to Mom.
都这么大的人了
So much for being a grownup.
是啊 我给她演了我的歌
Yeah, I played her the song.
是 那歌很火 你得照
Yes, and it's fire, and you will do it
贾马尔和你计划的那样表演 就这样
the way you and Jamal arranged it, end of story.
你们还能强迫我吗
How you gonna make me?
你能不能不要像个孩子一样 你才是小孩
Why don't you stop acting like a baby. You the baby!
你才是 你个乳臭未干的小孩 你就这样了
You the baby, the dumb little baby... that's what you do.
你个地中海秃头小孩
And you the semibaldheadedlooking baby.
闭嘴
Shut up!
现在 我面前站着谁 两个男孩还是两个女孩
Now, what did I have, two boys or two little girls?
因为你们听起来像两个娘炮
'Cause y'all sound like two sissies.
现在 我在投资者展示会回去的路上说了什么
Now, what did I tell y'all way back at that investor showcase?
嗯 你们不该做的就是
Hmm? What y'all not gonna do is come in between
挡我的财路
me and my money.
你们哥俩已经很久
Now, it's been too long since you and your brother
没在人前表演了
performed in front of the people.
这就是粉丝所要的
And that's what they want,
这也是我们要给他们的
and that's what we will give them.
你们就是想把我硬拉入
Y'all just trying to drag me
你们与卢修斯之间的矛盾
into a fight y'all are having with Lucious.
你特么给我滚过来 小子
Get your narrow ass back up here, boy.
别在我说话的时候走开
Don't you ever walk away from me.
我在试着阻止一个儿子
I'm trying to stop one son
去回击一个根本都不是我们厂牌的艺人
from clapping back at an artist that's not even on our label.
哼 哼
Mmhmm.
噢，我只是在试着
Oh. And I'm only trying
帮我另一个傻儿子
to help my other son get back to performing
在他的粉丝忘记他这号人之前
in front of his fans before they forget
重回舞台表演
how much they love his stupid ass.
嗯哼
Mmhmm.
如果你害怕
If you are afraid
跟着你爸爸对着干
of getting on the wrong side of your daddy...
那你也绝对不会想要跟你妈妈对着干
you don't want to get on the wrong side of your mama.
懂了吗
You feel me?
我说 你听懂我的话没
I said, do you feel me?
是 我懂了
Yeah, I feel you.
很好 过来
Good. Come here.
嗯
Mmm.
嘿 老妈
Hey, Ma...
把这该死的地方弄干净
Clean this damn place up.
闻起来跟屎一样
Smelling like ass in here!
下一次 进我的房子请拖鞋好吗
Next time, take your shoes off in my house, please.
闭嘴，哈基姆 你最好在我往这儿扔炸弹之前
Shut up, Hakeem. Boy, you better clean this place up before
把这儿弄干净 猪屎窝
I throw an acid bomb in here. Nastyass pigsty.
怎么样 大家 我是贾马尔 里昂
What's up, everybody? It's your boy, Jamal Lyon.
我想对你们的观看说谢谢
I want to say thank you so much for tuning in.
我们现在正在帝国极度流上直播
We are all the way live on Empire XStream.
这是我的弟弟 哈基姆
That's my baby brother, Hakeem.
我们在这儿真的只为了爱和光明
We are here truly for love and light.
所以为了你们 这首歌献给大家
So for all of y'all, this is for you.
谁都能在洗澡的时候
Anybody can perform in the shower
或者是在他该死的客厅里表演
or in the middle of his damn living room.
看看这个
Look at this.
这是什么 用户吗
What are those, the users?
看起来数字正在平稳上升
Looks like the numbers are staying steady.
是的，但是他们得继续往上冲才行
Yeah, but they need to go up.
哈基姆的观众都没在看
Hakeem's audience ain't even tuning in
因为他们不是来这听什么人权颂歌的
because they not here for this Kumbaya crap.
我们需要来点劲爆的
We need some fire in here.
好吧 随便 卢修斯 离我远点
Okay, whatever, Lucious. Get away from me.
好吧
Okay.
格拉姆怎么了
What happened to Gram, man?
里昂家的人不会从争斗中逃跑 我们要碾压他
Lyons don't run from beef. We crush that.
我不想和一个胆小鬼争 而且争的还是我前任
I don't need to be beefing over a chick who's my ex.
尤其在我马上要有新欢的时候
Especially when I'm about to have a new one.
什么
What?
内莎
Nessa?
嗯哼 我们谈了一会儿
Yeah. We been talking for a minute.
我今天就要把这事儿定下来
I'ma lock it down today.
好吧 我不想告诉你这个坏消息
Well, I hate to be the one to break it to you,
但是你的兄弟已经捷足先登了
but your brother already got that on lock.
我哥
My brother?
不是贾马尔
Not Jamal.
安德鲁
Dre.
不 安德鲁不会那样做的
Nah, Andre wouldn't do that.
快把你的女孩追回来
Man, you better get your girl back.
来吧 哥们
Come on, brother.
这是直播 孩子 无论他在生气什么
This is live, boy. Whatever he's mad at,
让他气 否则场面会更糟 知道吗
let him be mad, or it's gonna get worse, okay?
这怎么回事 哈基姆 这算怎么一回事
What the hell was that, Hakeem?! What the hell was that about?!
你明知道安德鲁搞上了我的女人
You got us doing this Mickey Mouse performance
却还找我来做这像米老鼠一样
about brotherhood when you know
兄弟合家欢的傻逼演出
Andre's giant ass crushing my girl!
你特么到底在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?!
安德鲁和内莎
Andre and Nessa!
这就是我说的 哈基姆
That's what I'm talking about! Hakeem,
我们可以找个另外的时间谈这个
we could have talked about this at a different time.
你还想否认
You're trying to deny it?
冷静点 好吗 我甚至都不知道你对内莎有意思
Calm down, okay? I didn't even know you were into Nessa.
你当然知道 我什么都不知道
Of course you knew! I didn't know nothing.
等等 等等 等等 你们都在干什么
Wait, wait, wait, what are y'all doing?!
不 不 不 不 不 不 不 不 不 我无所谓
No, no, no, no, no, no! No, no! I don't give a damn
你在生气什么
what you are pissed off about.
你现在把这事儿完全升级了 我想知道为什么
You took it to another level, and I want to know why!
这傻逼的演出一开始就是你的主意
Wackass performance was your idea in the first place!
我就不应该听你的话
I shouldn't have never listened to you.
你只是利用我做了一场表演
You just used me to do a performance
就因为你没种出去自己表演
'cause you can't get out there and do it yourself!
傻逼还想当真说唱歌手 我现在就杀了你
Fakeass wannabe MC! I will kill you right...
闭上你的狗屎嘴 作法自毙的人
Shut your big ass up, Frankenstein!
加油 加油
Come on! Come on!
继续录 不要停
Keep rolling! Keep filming!
不 停
No, stop!
关掉
Turn it off!
你到底什么毛病
What the hell is wrong with you?!
来人把这个插回去
Somebody plug this back in!
你不能只抱怨我 哈基姆 啥事都没有
You cannot just claim me, Hakeem... nothing happened!
我们没有一起唱那个二重唱 我们气场不合么
We didn't do that duet together? We didn't vibe together?
我的天哪 气场 气场 闭嘴
Oh my goodness, a vibe, a vibe! Shut up!
你们不要担心
Y'all, it's okay, don't worry about it,
因为哈基姆里昂 他只是在对某位女性
'cause Hakeem Lyon, he was just vibin'
散发气场 所以没事
to some female, so it's all good.
把摄像机关了 这都结束了
Turn these cameras off! This is over! A wrap!
所有人都出去
Everybody out!
小贱人
Pettyass dumb bitch!
闭上你愚蠢的臭嘴
Shut your Frank Ocean wannabeass up!
你个狗娘养的 把摄像机关了
You shut your fakeass wannabe... Turn these cameras off!
嗨 贝基 进来 请坐
Hello, Becky. Come in. Have a seat.
所以 提安娜
So, uh, Tiana...
很不幸的是 因为针对你的主打歌
unfortunately, there was a miscommunication
出现了一些误会
in your lead song, so...
我们决定延迟发布你的唱片
we're gonna have to postpone the release of your album.
不是 你什么意思 误会
No... What do you mean, a miscommunication?
好吧 泽维尔告诉我你录了 星光
Well, Xavier told me that you recorded Starlight...
某种程度上那算是告密
which that is lightweight snitchin',
但是我们后面再处理这个
but we gonna deal with that later.
我没有同意用那首歌
I did not sign off on that song.
所以现在我们要让你重回录音棚
So now we got to put you back in the studio
录制 我 那首我想要的歌
to record Me, The song I wanted.
所以 你跟我撒谎了
So... you lied to me?
没有 我相信那首歌
No. I believed in the song.
我不能和说谎的人一起工作 酷琦
I can't work with no liars, Cookie.
我想让她离开我的团队 什么
I want her off my team. What?
你认真的吗
Are you serious?
我是这里唯一一个为你争取的人
I'm the only one around here fighting for you.
是啊 看看这有什么好结果
Yeah, and look where it got me.
酷琦 她现在只是在气头上
T... Cookie, she's just mad right now.
请不要让我离开她的团队
Please don't take me off her team.
这可是你说的 贝基
You said it, Becky.
我们得给艺人他们想要的
We got to give the artist what they want. Now...
我可以试试和她谈谈 看能不能改变她的想法
I can try and talk to her and see if I can change her mind,
但是 这都是你自己造成的
but... you did this.
你要学会听话
You need to learn how to listen.
怎么了 我以为你喜欢这歌
What happened? I thought you liked the song.
我是喜欢
I did.
你为什么不支持我
So why didn't you have my back?
这只是生意
It's just business.
她在这儿 酷琦
There she is. Cookie,
你想把介绍给我一个非常好的朋友
I'd like to introduce you to a good friend of mine,
格斯 罗德里格斯
Gus Rodriguez.
你知道戴维斯女士吗
You know Ms. Davis.
哦 所以
Oh, so...
是这个意思啊 安吉洛
it's like this now, huh, Angelo?
我来就是为了道歉的 里昂女士
I'm here to apologize, Ms. Lyon.
里昂女士 戴维斯已经因为她过分热心的行为
Ms. Lyon, Officer Davis has been reprimanded
被训斥过了
for her overzealous behavior.
她希望那样足够歉意
She hopes that that will be sufficient,
而你不会投诉我们
and you won't choose to file a complaint.
我不会
I'm not.
啊 这怎么样了
Uh, what's going on here?
看着像是我们
It seems that we got
得到了一些和你没什么关系的调查相关的
some wrong information about an ongoing investigation
错误消息
that has nothing to do with you.
所以你说是谁告诉她来打压我的
So who you saying told her to put the squeeze on me?
我不能说 但是你一直都规规矩矩
I'm not at liberty to say, but you've been a model offender,
我这边觉得没必要扩大对你的限制
and my office sees no reason to extend your restrictions.
我和我兄弟在哥伦比亚打球的时候就认识了
I've known my man here since we balled at Columbia.
他说你是好人 所以你在我这里不会有麻烦
He says you're good people; you're good with me.
好的 我在前面等你
Okay. I'll wait for you out front.
好的 谢谢
All right, man, thanks.
三个月后再见 奥洛
I'll see you in three months, Hollo...
里昂小姐
Ms. Lyon.
给孩子们我的爱 夏琳娜
Give the kids my love, Sharlene.
所以你帮我费了些麻烦 是吧
So you went to a lot of trouble for me, huh?
我看到你儿子们今晚
I saw your boys tonight
在帝国极度流的情况了
on Empire XStream, and, uh...
我意识到一些关于你和你家庭的事
I realized something about you and your family.
是的 我确定整个世界都知道了
Yeah, I'm sure the whole world did.
好吧 我意识到 争斗
Well, I realized that... fighting
是你们家族的行为方式
is your family's way of life.
它像是流淌在你的血液里的
It's... it's like it's in your blood.
但你们都有一种概念
But somehow, y'all got the idea that I'm...
我不是一个斗士
I'm not a fighter.
听着 我现在不是试着和你们一起去战斗
Look, I am not trying to fight with you right now.
小女孩 我不是在说
Baby girl, I'm not talking about
和你并肩作战的事
fighting with you...
我是说为你而战
I'm talking about fighting for you.
如果那意味着和卢修斯作对 那好吧
And if that means going up against Lucious, well...
就这样吧
then so be it.
嗯哼
Hmm.
你把我一路从布朗斯维尔带出来
You got me all the way out in Brownsville.
我希望你准备好谈谈这事了
I hope you're ready to talk.
是的 我想谈这事
Yeah, I'm ready to talk.
你准备好过联邦证人保护项目下的生活了吗
You ready to be about that WITSEC life?
联邦证人保护项目 你昏头了吧
WITSEC? You must be smoking.
你不会打算在给我那具尸体后
You ain't gonna be walking around in the sunshine
还在光天化日之下到处晃吧
after giving me a body.
你没那么疯狂吧 我的老兄
Even you ain't that crazy, my G.
什么尸体
What body?
就是那具你和卢修斯
The one you and Lucious hid
藏在卡姆登的一块混凝土板下面的
in a slab of concrete back in Camden.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你知道我的意思
You know what I'm talking about.
听着 我不想和你捉迷藏了 肖恩
Look, I ain't the one to be playing with, Shine.
我在全方位向里昂家族施压
I'm squeezing the Lyon family on all sides.
让酷琦的假释官对她加强监管
Got Cookie's P.O. To tighten the leash on her, and I can
我也能随时这样对待你
turn that same heat on you anytime I want.
那听起来可不像感恩 塔里克
That don't sound like gratitude, Tariq.
尤其是我还打算
Especially when I'm about to make
早点给你欢庆圣诞节呢
Christmas come early for you.
那是谁
Who's that?
芙蕾达 盖茨
That's Freda Gatz.
那个在美国音乐奖上射击了贾马尔 里昂的说唱歌手吗
The rapper that shot Jamal Lyon at the ASAs?
就是她
Exactly.
你知道她的爸爸是谁吗
Do you know who her dad was?
记得弗兰克 盖哲思吗 我当然记得弗兰克
Remember Frank Gathers? Of course I remember Frank.
你 卢修斯和酷琦
You, Lucious and Cookie,
你过去还替他做事呢
you used to run material for him back in the day.
只是对外宣称的
Allegedly.
更重要的是 你知道她的爸爸
More importantly, you know her father
曾和卢修斯被一起关在BCC监狱里
was locked up with Lucious at the BCC.
你知道 他在那里被杀了
You know, he got killed up there.
现在 我不敢说这是不是一个巧合 或另有隐情
Now, I can't tell if it was a coincidence or... or what.
我不知道
I don't know.
所以你意思是卢修斯和这事儿有关吗
So you saying Lucious had something to do with it?
不是 我不是这意思
Nah, that's not what I'm saying.
实际上 我什么也没说
Actually, I ain't saying nothing.
我只是带着我的狗在这附近转悠
I'm just taking my dog for a walk through the neighborhood.
我知道你和肖恩今天见面的意图
I know what you was up to in that meeting with Shine today.
但是我也没有对你生气
I ain't mad at you, though.
那是个好主意
It was a good idea.
好吧 说到好主意的话
Well, when it comes to good ideas,
我从你那儿学了很多
let's just say I learned from the best.
我只是很高兴我能帮忙
Nah, I'm just glad I could help.
你知道 我可以一直帮忙的
I could continue being a help, you know.
肖恩需要一个艺人监理部总监
Shine's gonna need an A&R.
看看你
Look at you.
试着从这整件事中
Trying to get something for yourself
为你自己捞点好处
out of this whole thing.
我只是说说而已 是的
I'm just saying. Yeah.
我会考虑这件事的 好么
I'll think about it, all right?
听着 让我和我的伙伴们讨论一下
Look, let me talk to my boy for a minute.
好的
Okay.
她就待在你的胸口
I'ma place her right on your chest.
她太小了 我觉得我会伤着她
She's so tiny, I think I'm gonna break her.
不会 别担心
Nah, don't worry.
相信你自己
Just trust yourself.
就这样
Right there.
确定她的脑袋是好好放松的
Make sure her head is nice and relaxed.
你是正确的 爸爸
You were right, Dad.
是的
Yeah.
我不会让你就这样被整
I wasn't gonna let you get punked like that.
如果那意味着
And if that means you got to
你要和你的兄弟争斗的话 那么
go to war with your brothers, then...
就这样吧
so be it.
你对贾马尔的看法也是正确的
You were right about Jamal, too.
是的 我知道
Yeah, I know.
所以这意味着
So this means I don't have to
我不必和你再争吵了吗
play tugofwar with you no more?
我也不想的
I wasn't trying to do that.
你想给贝拉最好的 对吗
You want what's right for Bella, right?
想要为她创造一个好的世界
Want to set the world up for her.
但是我需要再次从音乐上找回我自己
But I need to find myself again, musically.
但是现在和肖恩的关系太僵了
But things are just so tense with Shine right now.
啊 别担心他 我搞定了
Ah, don't worry about him. I took care of that.
看看她
Look at her.
在你的臂弯里熟睡
Sound asleep in your arms.
这是第一次她没在我怀里哭喊
It's the first time she's not screaming in my arms.
知道为什么吗
Know why?
你的霸气又回来了
You got your swagger back.
来吧
Come on.
让我们把她放在这里
Let's put her down over here.
当你照顾一个婴儿时
When you swaddle a baby,
你要把角落折叠好
you want to bend down the top of the corner
像是摆一个V形
like you're making a nice V.
然后你把她的头顶
Then you put her head, the top of her head,
放在那里 就是那里 最上面
right there, right there, at the top of that.
好的 你做到了
Okay. You got it.
她信任你
She trusts you.
是的 撑着她的脖子
Yeah, support that neck.
我来 噢
I got you. Oh...
噢 小宝贝
Oh, little baby.
噢 你做到了
Oh, you got it,
你做到了 你做到了
you got it, you got it.
她很好 很舒服
She's good, she's good.
好的
All right.
让我们来谈谈你的音乐
Let's talk about this music of yours.
我有一些想法
I have some thoughts about
关于你合作的人选
who you should and shouldn't be working with.
是的 你应该和肖恩一起做一些歌曲
And, yeah, you should do some songs with Shine,
但只做一些
but not all of 'em.
可能我会给你制作歌曲
Maybe I'll produce you again.
把你变成一个超级毁灭者
Turn you into a destroyer of souls.